Julija Rezanovica

Flat 3 Campbell House, Churchill Gardens, London, SW1V 3HS

07482777316 <u>juliyarezanovich@gmail.com</u>

N.I. Number SS543947D

Personal Statement

A responsible, creative and highly organized individual with a professional attitude and excellent work ethic. Willing to learn and develop new skills. Focused and proactive approach with the ability to adapt and prioritize tasks.

I have run Culture and Marketing Departments in University's Parliament, organising events, working on projects for my University and other High Education Institutions. I have as well wrote articles for vast number of exhibitions.

Key Skills

- Great Personality
- Russian, Latvian, Belorussian, Ukrainian, English speaker (Swedish and Mandarin beginner)
- Responsible
- Sales Skills
- Creative writer
- Eager to learn, learn fast.
- Great interpersonal skills

- Adaptable
- 5 years of luxury experience.
- Professional, positive and outstanding attitude
- Team Leadership and Management Skills
- Great punctuality and Attendance record
- Goal oriented.

Employment History

Luxury watch specialist Nov.2017- Present

"Omega luxury watches" 260 Regent Street, London,

- Achieving monthly, quarterly and annual sales targets
- Managing stock methodically transfers, stock audits, bar-coding, etc.
- General administration replying to client inquiries and assisting with monthly reports
- Preparing banking analysis /submitting petty cash expenditure
- Update and maintain client book using Microsoft Excel
- Attend boutique and watchmaking events network and liaise with VIP clients
- Book-in repair services using internal client data capture system
- Providing new-comers a necessary training
- Actively correspond with clients and assist with resolving complaints

Luxury sales consultant Feb.2017-Oct.2017

"Salvatore Ferragamo in Harrods" 87-135 Brompton Road, London

- Supporting managers with emails and stock check.
- Keeping track of transfers and items going to Personal Shopping.
- Working as a team player.
- Supporting boutique as a staff, when it's necessary.
- Learning specifics about materials used in Ferragamo collections and completing tests.
- Working on CRM folders, separating customers in different categories and contacting them accordingly to their interests.

Luxury sales consultant Nov.2016-Feb.2017

"Freedom Recruitment Agency" 22 Stukeley Street, London

- Working in Browns Fashion, Stella McCartney and Weekend Max Mara as temporary sales consultant.
- Supporting the team on a daily basis in achieving their targets.
- Supporting stock controllers keeping stock in perfect condition.

Luxury Sales consultant Aug.2016-Nov.2016

- Driving sales with passion for luxury fashion.
- Approachable nature and discreet service by representing this exclusive Lingerie & Swimwear brand.
- Building a strong, long lasting relationship with customers, creating a CRM file.
- Delivering the very best shopping experience.
- Proactively replenishing stock and maintaining an impeccably kept shop floor.

Luxury Sales consultant Apr.2015-Aug. 2016

"Casio London" 5B The Market building, Covent Garden, London, WC2E 8RA

- Positively meeting and greeting customers giving them pleasant atmosphere.
- Representing the brand ethos and philosophy "Never give up".
- Working as a team player, supporting colleagues and the store.
- Showing an excellent knowledge of product in the store.
- Following the CASIO-G Journey.
- · Going extra mile in all daily tasks.

Photographer Jan.2014-Jan.2015

"Julia plus Julian"

- Have worked as a freelance photographer, specializing on love story and wedding photography.
- Have made photo shoots in Sweden, Latvia and Spain.

Actress/Model Jan.2013-Dec.2013

Casting Collective Agency

- Have worked with an independent fashion photographers and fashion designers.
- Attended and participated in many fashion shows as a catwalk model.
- Participated as a stylist in photo shoots helping to create certain looks.
- Participated in promo videos.
- Assisted in writing scenarios

Head of Culture Department

Sep.2010-Feb.2014

"Baltic International Academy" Lomonosova Iela 1/4, Riga, Latvia.

- Worked in Baltic International Academy parliament.
- Organizing public events, university events.
- Was organizing and leading art exhibitions.
- Responsibilities of leader included the following: involvement of sponsors, team building, and distribution of responsibilities, budgeting, writing projects and solving common student problems.
- Press release writing.
- Writing articles for university art gallery exhibitions.

Education & Training

Baltic International Academy

2010-Present

- Project Management in Culture.
- Writing projects, organizing events. Marketing, PR projects.

Drama School 2010-2011

Certificate of Drama School

Sales training 2009-2010

Understanding of customer needs, how to increase sales profit and leadership skills.

High School Daugavpils City Center Gymnasium

2004-2010

 GCSE (equivalent A Grade): Math, Science, Information Technology, Geography, World History, Chemistry, Biology, Business Economics

Hobbies

Creative writing, poem writing, drawing, dancing, photography, reading books, philosophy, science, piano, taekwondo, yoga, chess, movies, cooking, pool, skating, travelling, cycling, ice skiing, shopping, picnic, developing new skills.